[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the hottest part of the computer?", "correct_answer": "CPU", "incorrect_answers": ["Fan", "RAM", "Hard Drive"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What atomic number does Calcium have?", "correct_answer": "20", "incorrect_answers": ["21", "22", "19"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Marys occupation in the 1998 comedy movie Theres Something About Mary?", "correct_answer": "Orthopedic surgeon", "incorrect_answers": ["Pediatrician", "Veterinarian", "Neurosurgeon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these four Calvin Klein fragrances was created first in 1985?", "correct_answer": "Obsession", "incorrect_answers": ["Truth", "Euphoria", "cK be"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This highly aromatic perennial herb, native to southern Europe, is widely used in salads, meat and potato balls, and its flavor is similar to that of anise.", "correct_answer": "Fennel", "incorrect_answers": ["Licorice", "Ginger", "Hyssop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although the grizzly bear is on the flag of this state, the last grizzly was shot there in 1922.", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Nevada", "Oregon", "Idaho"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to reach the South Pole?", "correct_answer": "Amundsen", "incorrect_answers": ["Scott", "Henson", "Peary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Wedding Crashers, Todd made a painting of John holding a leaf over his privates.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The process of photosynthesis is carried out by which of these major cell organelles?", "correct_answer": "Chloroplasts", "incorrect_answers": ["Mitochondria", "Ribosomes", "Vacuoles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character in the movie Another Cinderella Story is based on the stepmother from the classic Cinderella story?", "correct_answer": "Dominique", "incorrect_answers": ["Natalia", "Bree", "Britt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Orca (Killer Whale) is the largest species of dolphin.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This device, consisting of one or more film projectors mechanically linked to a movie camera, can be used for making special effects for motion pictures or for copying and restoring old film material.", "correct_answer": "Optical Printer", "incorrect_answers": ["Double Headed Projector", "Optical Imaging Camera", "Duel Picture Setup"]}]